Guide to the Florine and Ettie Stettheimer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1907-1974; Series IV; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  - MISCELLANEOUS MATERIAL
    - Photographs of Alwyn Court and the Stettheimer's friends by Carl Van Vechten, 1932-44, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 175-77)
    - Photographs, unidentified, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - Scrapbooks: "Theater Records of Ettie Stettheimer", 1907-09 (Box 10, Folder 179-80)
  - OVERSIZE
    - Photographs of stage sets for Four Saints in Three Acts, 1934 Mar 10, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 181-82)